J. Paul Getty had a fortune. Everyone else paid the price.
All the Money in the World is a crime, history,
thriller film directed by Ridley Scott.
The story of the kidnapping of 16-year-old John Paul Getty III and the desperate attempt by his
devoted mother to convince his billionaire grandfather Jean Paul Getty to pay the ransom.
Gail Harris, played by Michelle Williams.
Fletcher Chase, played by Mark Wahlberg.
Jean Paul Getty, played by Christopher Plummer.
John Paul Getty III, played by Charlie Plummer.
Cinquanta, played by Romain Duris.
Oswald Hinge, played by Timothy Hutton.
All the Money in the World is a 2017 biographical crime thriller film
directed by Ridley Scott and written by David Scarpa.
Based on John Pearson's 1995 book Painfully Rich: The
Outrageous Fortunes and Misfortunes of the Heirs of J.
Paul Getty, it depicts the events surrounding the 1973 kidnapping of John Paul Getty III
and the refusal of his grandfather, the multi-billionaire oil tycoon J.
Paul Getty, to cooperate with the kidnappers' extortion demands.
The film stars Michelle Williams as Gail Harris Getty, John Paul Getty III's mother, Christopher
Plummer as Getty, and Mark Wahlberg as Fletcher Chace, an adviser of the Getty family.
Principal photography began in March 2017 and was completed in
August, with the release scheduled for December 8.
Kevin Spacey originally played Getty, but sexual misconduct allegations were made against him two months after filming, so Plummer, Scott's original preferred casting choice
for the role, was cast in the role and, one month prior to the rescheduled Christmas release, the 22 scenes featuring Getty were reshot within eight days.
It was later reported that Wahlberg was paid $1.5 million for the reshoots, while Williams was
only paid $1,000, which sparked a debate on the gender pay gap in Hollywood.
The film premiered at the Samuel Goldwyn Theater in Beverly Hills on December 18, 2017,
followed by a United States theatrical release by TriStar Pictures on December 25.
It received generally favorable reviews, many of which praised the
performances, and grossed $57 million against a $50 million budget.
Plummer received particular acclaim, and he was nominated for the Academy
Award for Best Supporting Actor for his work in the film.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, rome,
italy, kidnapping, 1970s, based on true story.
The tone is intense.